M.Janastin

Email: m.janastin@gmail.com Mobile: +91 871-090-0980

Objective

I am looking forward to an opportunity where I can utilize my potential and experiences in contributing effectively to the success of the organization, continuously working towards success, and adding value to my employers and project teams.

Software Skills

MS Office Basic Dreamweaver Basic Photoshop

Experience

March 2012 - August 2013 Client Accounts Executive isous | Bangalore

Work directly with customers via telephone, and email to describe software products and web services in order to persuade potential and current customers to purchase new products and services.

Educate customers on product offerings and services to improve their "on-line presence" and explain pricing and answer their questions.

Co-ordinate between client & production team to ensure project delivery on time.

Assist them in setting up of accounts, resolving queries (web based)

September 2013 - February 2015 Sr. Client Accounts Executive Isous | Bangalore

Allocating tasks to staff & ensuring the performance of the staff is of a high standard

Follow up with customer via telephone or email following initial sales contact.

Provide support to customers, handle inquires, provide resolutions

Manage the flow of day-to-day operations

Carrying out performance reviews

Personal Qualities

Confident with positive attitude and hardworking, quick learner can adapt to different situations.

Friendly, extrovert person who loves to meet new people.

I enjoy working in multicultural environment facing new challenges.

Education

2005 - Bachelor in Computer Applications (BCA)

Indian Academy College, Bangalore

2002-2005 Pre University Course (PUC)

Govt PU College, Raichur

2001-2002 Secondary School Leaving Certificate (S.S.L.C)

Dr.E.A.Seamands High School, Raichur

Strengths

Team player

Comprehensive problem solving ability

Ability to grasp new skills.

Confident and Devoted

Adaptive to any working conditions

Good interpersonal skills

Personal Profile

Father's Name : K.Murugesh

Date of Birth : 29th March 1987

Languages : English, Kannada, Tamil, Hindi.

Hobbies : Listening music.

Nationality: Indian

Address : 1st D Main, 5th Cross,

Gokula 1st Stage, Yeshwanthpur

Bangalore - 560 022

Declaration

I consider myself familiar with all aspects and I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place : Bangalore

Date : M.Janastin